ostoto.com 2019-05-05

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to OSToto and we take it seriously. In this Privacy Policy, we’ve described what data/information we collect, how we use it and how we protect it. This privacy policy governs your use of this website, including ostoto.com subdomain sites and the services/software available through these websites, our mobile websites. So we recommend that you read this privacy policy carefully in order to understand what OSToto does with your personal information and personal data.

By visiting ostoto.com, you consent to the information practices described in this statement. The terms “you”, “your”, “user” refer to our customers. The terms “we”, us”, “our” refer to OSToto.

## What Information/Data Do We Collect

We collect information directly from the customers, third parties like our purchase platform and Google Analytics, and might include:

1) **Your contact information.** When you log in the forum, contact us via email, register our software, or leave your feedback in the website, we might collect that information, including your name, email address, phone number, profile photo you upload, comments, and any other contact information you give us.

2) **Your payment information.** When you bought our software in the online shopping cart, we may connect your bank and credit account information, mailing address, information about your business and any other information you give us.

3) **IP address, geolocation.** Information through Cookies and other tracking technologies might include your IP address, geolocation.

4) **Information you share on our website.** If you share your opinion with us on our comment section, post on our forum, send feedback to us, we might collect the public information for software and website improvement and better services.

5) **Other information.** When you use OSToto desktop client, we will get several permissions and collect personal information or non-personal information in order to serve you better with our software. When you ask for online help, send feedback to our database, you might need to offer information about your hardware devices, pictures that show your issues, and more software usage information and statistics to analyze and troubleshoot your problems.

## How We Use Your Information

We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party. We only use your information:

* To provide services to you, communicate with you about your use of our software.

* To improve our website, software and services. For example, we might send you surveys to know your opinions on using our software. Participation in the surveys is voluntary.

* To better understand how you access and use our website and our services, both on an aggregated and individualized basis, for our internal purposes, and for other research and analytical purposes.

* For marketing purpose. For example, we might send you emails about our special promotions and offers.

We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

## How We Protect Your Information

We store your information on our secure servers. Any payment transactions is processed on authorized platform that is SSL encrypted. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to us; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent un-authorized access.

## Your Choices and Rights

You may, of course, opt out of receiving any emails that might be sent to provide special offers and promotions mentioned above by clicking “Unsubscribe” in any email. We do not share information with third parties, or sell your information to any un-authorized entities for their independent marketing or promotional purposes.

## Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Mechanisms

We and our third-party service providers may use cookies and other tracking mechanisms such as JavaScript, web beacons to track information about your use of our website and services. When you access our services, we may track and obtain certain types of information such as your IP address, geolocation, time and date of access, language use, the type of browser used, the device type used to browse our website, your click of certain button or links, and the page(s) you requested. These technologies help us better understand our user behavior, count the number of visitors, tell us how you move around our website.

Another kind of cookies is the functionality cookies which are used to recognize you when you return to our website. In this case, you are identified as a returning visitor. It helps remember your preference such as the language and region.

You may, however, disable certain tracking by modifying your browser settings. Different browsers use different ways to disable the cookies, please check yours on your own. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, or how to disable cookies altogether. If you are not sure how to do it, please contact your browser provider for help. Please note that certain features of our website or services will not be available once cookies are disabled.

## Do Not Track Signals

Our systems do not currently respond or take any action with respect to the browser “do-not-track” signals or requests. Your may disable certain tracking as described above such as by disabling cookies.

## Transferring Your Data

OSToto sells product all over the world. As such, we and our service providers may transfer your personal information to the jurisdiction that may not provide equivalent levels of data protection as your home jurisdiction. When personal information is transferred from the European Economic Area (EEA), we take special safeguards to ensure that the protection travels with the data, including having standard clauses approved by the European Commission in our contracts with parties that receive information outside the EEA.

## Children’s Privacy

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we adopted the following privacy policy regarding children under the age of 13 years (or the age of 14 for anyone living in Spain or South Korea):

1)We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from such children.

2)We do not knowingly allow such children to register.

3)If we become aware that we collected personal information from such children without parent consent, we will take steps to erase that information ASAP.

## Contact Us, Update Your Information, Or Opt Out of Our Services

If you submit incorrect information to us and want to correct and update it, or you don’t want to receive any further subscriptions and want to determinate the services we offered, or you have any privacy related questions, and in any case that you need to contact us, just contact us via the email address: contact#ostoto.com (replace # with @)

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

We may change the Privacy Policy from time to time to make it applicable to related laws and regulations. Any changes or updates will be posted on our website. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our software and services means that you agree to the changes of the privacy. We will not materially reduce your rights without taking steps to bring such changes to your attention.

## EEA Customers Only

We make the below additional details about processing the personal information of EEA customers.

1) **You can ask us to confirm whether we are processing your personal data.** And if needed, you can request us to give you a copy of the data. We will provide you with the information that you want to receive to our best. And of course, you don’t have to pay for the copy of your information unless your request is unfounded, respective or excessive, in which case we will charge a reasonable amount in the circumstances.

2) **You can ask us to correct any inaccurate or incomplete data.** If we cannot action a request to correct your data, we will let you know and explain why.

3) **You can ask us to erase your data in certain conditions** where:

it is no longer necessary for the purpose for which it was originally collected or processed;

we are processing your data based on your consent, and you withdraw that consent;

you object to the processing and we do not have an overriding legitimate interest for continuing;

your data has been unlawfully processed;

your data must be erased to comply with a legal obligation;

the data was processed to offer information society services to a child.

4) **You can ask us to stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes.** We will stop without any reasons to refuse as soon as we receive your request.
